insidemex.com 2014-12-16

# Privacy Policy | Inside Mexico

**Insidemex.com Privacy Policy**

We at Insidemex.com, Inc. want you to feel safe online. For that reason, we follow a privacy policy that applies to all of the products, services and websites offered by Editorial Kilimanjaro, SA de CV, Insidemex.com's parent company.  In line with that policy, we want to let you know how we treat personal information that we collect and receive from visitors to and registered users of the website [www.insidemex.com](http://www.insidemex.com/) . Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address or phone number. 

This Privacy Policy covers the following: 

  * The information we collect and use, including how we generally use that information.
  * What we share and disclose and why and to whom.
  * What " Cookies" and "Web beacons" are and how we use them.
  * How to update and delete your account information.
  * How you will be notified of changes to our Privacy Policy.
  * How and whom to contact if you have questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy.

Insidemex.com' Privacy Policy applies only to websites and services that are owned and operated by Editorial Kilimanjaro, SA de CV. While other websites may be displayed as search results or links from within Insidemex.com, those sites are owned and operated by others, and they may have different privacy policies. When linking from Insidemex.com to other websites, if you have privacy concerns, we urge you to review the privacy policies of those sites. 

It's also important to note that this Privacy Policy does not apply to information that you post, yourself, in public areas of the Insidemex.com website. For example, if you choose to let other people see your name, photo and email address on your Profile page, or if you post information or comments on a discussion board, that information will be made public. Your messages and other information you make available in public areas of the Insidemex.com website will be seen by people and organizations not related to or controlled by Insidemex.com, and may be used by others to contact you. 

**Information Collection and Use**

We collect personal information from you whenever you interact with Insidemex.com, such as when you: 

  * Register with Insidemex.com,
  * Use our products or services,
  * Enter promotions or sweepstakes, and
  * Visit web pages on Insidemex.com or on the websites of certain of our partners.

We may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. 

When you register, we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender and ZIP code. Once you register with Insidemex.com and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. You are free to use Insidemex.com without registering or setting up a personal Insidemex.com Account; however, some of our services and web pages are available only to those who are registered members. 

We automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, Insidemex.com cookie information and the pages you request. 

We use your personal information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. In short, the information you provide us can help us to understand how to make the website more convenient and useful to you. 

In we provide access to your personal information only to Insidemex.com employees and contractors who we believe need that access in order to do their jobs and to provide products or services to you. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

We do not rent, sell or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you request, when we have your permission or under the following circumstances: 

  * We may sometimes share aggregate non-personal information with third parties such as the media, advertisers and government agencies. This aggregate information is typically in the form of statistics, such as numbers of Insidemex.com members who live in a particular state or fall within a particular age group. Such aggregate information is gathered from individual Insidemex.com members' information but is not traceable to any specific identifiable Insidemex.com member.
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
  * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the Insidemex.com terms of use or as otherwise required or permitted by law.
  * If Insidemex.com is acquired by or merged with or into another company, we will provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

**Our Advertisers**

We do not share your personal information with our advertisers, unless you have explicitly, in writing, requested us to do so. However, the advertising we display is targeted to users of particular services and content. So if you view or click on a targeted ad, the advertiser (or other companies affiliated with the advertiser) may assume that you meet the targeting criteria, for example, women ages 50-60 from a particular geographic area or with children or grandchildren of a certain age. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

Insidemex.com, like many websites, uses cookies to prepare customized Web pages for you. A cookie is a file containing a string of code that we transfer to your computer's hard drive, to be kept there for later use. With cookies in place, whenever you use your Web browser (such as Internet Explorer, AOL or Mozilla Firefox) to connect to Insidemex.com, our systems are able to recognize you. This enables Insidemex.com to present you with custom Web pages. So, for example, instead of seeing just a generic welcome page, you see a welcome page with your name on it and information that relates to where you live (your ZIP code) and products or services that reflect your interests. 

In addition to Insidemex.com's cookies, when you visit Insidemex.com your computer may receive cookies from our advertisers and from other sites displayed as search results or links. The cookies inserted by those third parties are not covered by Insidemex.com' Privacy Policy, but rather, by the policies of those advertisers and outside websites. 

You can set up your browser to reject cookies or tell you when a cookie has been sent. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of Insidemex.com' interactive features, and we hope you will leave them turned on. 

Insidemex.com also uses web beacons (also known as action tags or single pixel gifs) to access Insidemex.com cookies inside and outside our Web pages and in connection with Insidemex.com products and services. A web beacon is a transparent image placed on a web page that sends a signal when a person visits that page. This enables us to assess the popularity and effectiveness of the material posted on the Insidemex.com website. We may also use web beacons in connection with e-mails sent to Insidemex.com members, to let us know whether and when the e-mail was opened. No personal information is transmitted through web beacons. 

**Third-party Ad Serving**

Insidemex.com contracts with third party companies to help us make sure that our content and advertising are relevant and effective, and to analyze how visitors use our site. To do this, we use Web beacons and cookies provided by our marketing company on this site. The type of information we collect includes, for example, the pages you visited at Insidemex.com. This information helps us learn things like what pages are most attractive to our visitors, which products are most interesting and what kinds of offers our visitors like to see. Although our third party marketing partners manage the information coming from our site on our behalf, we control how that data may and may not be used. If you do not want to help us learn how to improve our site, products, offers and marketing strategy, you can "opt-out" of allowing us to analyze such data by sending an email to [support@insidemex.com](mailto:support@insidemex.com). 

The ads on Insidemex.com pages are delivered to you by OpenX, our web advertising partner. Information about your visit to Insidemex.com, such as number of times you have viewed an ad, is used to serve ads to you whenever you visit Insidemex.com. For more information about OpenX, cookies and how to opt out, please click here <http://www.openx.org/privacy/market>

Insidemex.com may utilize third party advertising companies to serve a portion of the ads on the site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information about your visit to our site in order to provide relevant offers. You can find out more information about this practice and your choices concerning this practice at <http://networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. 

**Your Ability to Update and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences**

You can update your Insidemex.com Account Information, including your biographical and Profile information, at any time, by going to the Edit my Profile questions page and the Account Settings page. 

We reserve the right to send you certain important communications relating to the Insidemex.com service, such as service announcements and administrative messages, throughout the term of your personal Insidemex.com account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving these important communications. 

You can terminate your Insidemex.com account at any time by sending a request using the feedback form. 

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy may be changed from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Insidemex.com account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

**Questions and Suggestions**

If you have questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, please send us an email at [support@insidemex.com](mailto:support@insidemex.com). You may also send us physical mail at: 

Editorial Kilimanjaro 

Tonala 194, Int H 

Colonia Roma, Mexico, DC 06700 

Effective Date: February  16, 2009
